A Finding Aid to the James Brooks Papers, 1909-2010, bulk 1930-2010, in the Archives of American Art AAA.jamebroo
Archives of American Art
- Subject Files, 1926-2001; Series 6; 2 Linear feet Boxes 3-5, OV 20
  - Projects, Mural (Box 4)
    - Hempstead, N.Y. Post Office, circa 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - LaGuardia Airport, Flight (Box 5)
      - Explanation of Flight including Medium Used in Painting the Mural, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Landmarks Preservation Commission Report, circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Notes, circa 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Publicity, circa 1940-2001 (Box 5, Folder 4-10)
      - Record Book, circa 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 11)
        Includes time, date, materials and media, dimensions, models, and inventory of materials.
    - Little Falls, N.J. Post Office, 1938-1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Little Falls, N.J .Post Office and Woodside, L.I., Library, Account Book, 1934-1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Records costs, materials, and methods.
    - Woodside, L.I., Library, 1936-1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Projects, Painting Commission – Mobil Oil Corporation Headquarters, Fairfax, VA, circa 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - References from Brooks for Other Artists, circa 1973-1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, circa 1966-1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Teaching, Miscellaneous Locations, circa 1947-1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Teaching, Pratt Institute, circa 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Teaching, Queens College, circa 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Teaching, University of Pennsylvania, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Transatlantic Trip on Saturnia, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Oversized Lettering by Brooks from Box 4, Folder 38, 1930-1934 (Box OV 20)
- Personal Business Records, 1932-1992; Series 7; 1 Linear feet Boxes 5-6
  This series records transactions concerning Brooks’ artwork – conservation, gifts, loans, sales, and shipping. Gallery records include agreements, consignments, lists, receipts, etc. Also found are personal tax returns and an account book regarding early lettering work and income.
  Similar documentation may be found in some subject files (Series 6). Business records dated after Brooks' death that concern his artwork are found with the Charlotte Parks papers (Series 11).
  - Accounts for Lettering, 1932-circa 1935 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Appraisals, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Art Supplies (Sources, Services), circa 1977-1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Bills, Paid, 1958-1966 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Conservation, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Contract Form, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Gallery Records (Box 5)
    - Alex Rosenberg Gallery, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Berenson Gallery, 1960s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Berry-Hill, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Carone Gallery, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Lerner-Heller, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Martha Jackson Gallery, 1960s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Gifts, 1980-1991 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Insurance, 1949-1957 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Loans to Exhibitions, 1962-1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mailing Lists, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - Names for Paintings and Lists of Used Names, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Photo Lists, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Prices, circa 1970-1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Prints, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sales, 1966-1991 (Box 6, Folder 8-11)
  - Sales, Samuel M. Kootz Gallery Inc., 1961-1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Shipping Receipts, circa 1960-1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Shipping Receipts, Samuel M. Kootz Gallery Inc., circa 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Studio Expenses, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Tax Returns, 1946-1958 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Warehouse, 1966-1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Printed Material, 1928-1992; Series 8; 4.8 Linear feet Boxes 6-11, OV 21-OV 22
  Most printed material mentions Brooks or includes reproductions of his work; a small amount concerns other artists – friends, former students, and a few others. Articles include reviews and feature stories that appeared in newspapers and periodicals. Miscellaneous printed items consist of book jackets and calendars featuring reproductions of Brooks’ paintings, conference programs, announcements of shows for which Brooks served as a juror, an exhibition prospectus and entry form, political and anti-war tracts, and advertisements for Brooks exhibitions.
  Printed material, arranged by record type, is alphabetized by folder title.
  - Announcements of Lectures, Symposia, Miscellaneous Events, 1950s-1980s (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Articles, 1928-1992; Oversized material housed in OV 21. (Box 6, Folder 19-30)
  - Articles, 1981-1992 (Box 7, Folder 1-6)
  - Auction Catalogs, 1961-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Collection Catalogs, 1961-1985 (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, 1951-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10-16)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Checklists, circa 1936-1953 (Box 7, Folder 17-23)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Checklists, 1954-1963 (Box 8, Folder 1-19)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Checklists, 1963-1977 (Box 9, Folder 1-18)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Checklists, 1977-1991 (Box 10, Folder 1-13)
  - Invitations, 1965-1985 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Maps, 1940s-1950s (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Items, circa 1958-1965 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Museum Publications, 1952-1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Periodicals, 1950-1960 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Periodicals, It Is (nos. 1-6), 1958-1965 (Box 10, Folder 19-21)
  - Press Releases, 1957-1992 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Print Catalogs and Print Portfolio Announcements, 1970-1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Print Workshops, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Reproductions, Artwork by Brooks, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Reproductions, Artwork by Others, undated; Oversized material housed in OV 22. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Statements on Modern Art, 1950; undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Articles from Box 6, Folders 19-21, circa 1943-1951 (Box OV 21)
  - Oversized Reproductions of Artwork by Others from Box 11, Folder 4, undated (Box OV 22)
- Artwork, 1930s-1992; Series 9; 0.2 Linear feet Box 11
  Artwork by Brooks is comprised primarily of drawings in pencil and ink, loose and in two undated sketchbooks. Volume 1 is comprised of pencil sketches, mostly of figures and heads; Volume 2 consists of abstract compositions drawn in ink. Also found are "telephone doodles." Work by others consists of an ink drawing with watercolor wash by Paul Fligel inscribed to Brooks, an ink drawing of his sculpture by Adolph Gottlieb, three pencil drawings of Brooks by Philip Guston, two silhouettes of Brooks by William King, and a gouache painting on paper by an unidentified artist.
  - By Brooks (Box 11)
    - Drawings in Pencil and Ink, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Drawings in Pencil and Ink; Bookplate (print), 1930s-1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Sketch in Tempera, Mural Project, The Acquisition of Long Island, Woodside Library, 1930s (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Sketchbooks, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Telephone Doodles, undated (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
  - By Other Artists, 1948; undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Photographic Materials, 1909-2000s; Series 10; 4.1 Linear feet Boxes 11-15
  Photographic materials consist of photographs, digital prints, negatives, slides, and color transparencies. Subjects are artwork by Brooks, exhibition installations, people, places, and miscellaneous subjects.
  Photographs of people include Brooks, Park, and others. Among the identified individuals are: Barry Adabody, L. Adams, Giogrio Cavallon, Julie and Peter Cochran, Sivon Conaty, Cile Downs, Betty and Julian Eisenstein, Ruth Judge, Judy Braude Kahn, Ibram and Ernestine Lassaw, Conrad and Anita Marcarelli, Sanford and Arloie McCoy, Tino and Ruth Nivola, John and Estelle Opper, Barbara Park, Syd Solomon, and the Watsons. In addition, there is a copy of Nina Leen’s 1950 portrait of “The Irascibles” that appeared in Life. Also of note is a picture of unidentified attendees at a dinner at LaGuardia Airport on the occasion of the dedication of Flight.
  Among the places appearing are Brooks’ homes and studios in Montauk, New York, and East Hampton, New York. Views of the Middle East, taken during World War II, include Brooks and army colleagues, scenery, and views of local people engaged in daily activities. Travel pictures are of Maine, Italy, California and Oregon; those taken in Oregon include some of Park’s relatives. Miscellaneous subjects are cars, pets, lettering and type.
  This series is arranged by subject; within each subject, filing is alphabetical by folder title. Most of the material has been removed from binders and placed into archival folders. All original order has been maintained.
  - Artwork by Brooks (Box 11)
    All files may include photographic prints, digital prints, slides, negatives, and/or transparencies.
    - Artwork by Brooks (executed 1930s-1960s), circa 1933-2000s (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Artwork by Brooks (executed 1970-1974; slides), 1970s (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Artwork by Brooks (executed 1975-1987) and Exhibition Installation (1981), 1970s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Paintings and Drawings of the Middle East produced for the Army Artists' Program of the U.S. Army Historical Division (executed 1942-1945), 1997; 1940s (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper, La Guardia Mural (executed 1930s-1942), 1930s-circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1946-1949), 1940s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1950-1954), 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 21-23)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1955-1959), 1950s-1960s (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1960-1961), 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1962-1963), 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1964-1966), 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1967-1969), 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1970-1974), 1970s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 12-14)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1974-1979), 1970s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Paintings/Works on Paper (executed 1980-1986), 1980s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - Works on Paper (executed 1947-1980s), 1960s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Works on Paper (executed 1951-1986), 1970s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 4-7)
    - WPA Mural, The Acquisition of Long Island, Woodside Library, circa 1938-1942 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - WPA Mural, Flight, LaGuardia Airport (executed 1938-1942), undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - WPA Mural, Flight, LaGuardia Airport (executed 1938-1942), circa 1979-1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - WPA Mural, Flight, LaGuardia Airport, Restoration and Rededication Ceremony 18), 1980; 1 Photographic albums (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - WPA Mural, Hempstead, N.Y. Post Office (designed 1934; not executed), circa 1930s (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - WPA Mural, Labor and Leisure, Little Falls, N.J. Post Office (executed 1938), undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Installations; Family Portrait, 1982; Work by Other Artists, circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 14-17)
    - Artwork by Brooks (executed 1950s-1970s) for Slide Lecture, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Exhibition Installations, Kootz Gallery; Martha Jackson Gallery, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition Installations, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Exhibition Installations, 1972-1981 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
    - Exhibition Installations, 1985-1992 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
    - Exhibition Installations, 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - People (Box 14)
    - Brooks, 1909-1910; 1940s-1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Brooks with Colleagues in Egypt; Views of People, Daily Life and Landscapes, 1942-1945 (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
    - Brooks with Others, 1940s-1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Brooks and Park, 1950-1984 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Brooks and Park with Others, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Others, Identified, 1937-1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Others, Unidentified, 1940s-1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Places (Box 14)
    - Brooks' Homes, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Brooks' East Hampton Studio, 1994; undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Huckstep and Atlantic Crossing (U.S. Army), 1942 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Italy, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Maine, 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - The Middle East (Box 14)
      - Bengazi, 1942-1945 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Egypt, 1942-1945 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Palestine, 1942-1945 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Unidentified Locations, 1942-1945 (Box 14, Folder 24-26)
      - Unidentified Locations, 1942-1945 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
    - Montauk House and Studio, 1954; undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Montauk House Move to Springs (slides), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Oregon and California Trip; Oregon, 1968; undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Springs House and Studio, circa 1968-1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified, circa 1967-1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects, 1969; undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects, Lettering and Type, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects, 1949; undated; 9 rolls of negatives (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Katie and Everett at Headeck House, Charles at Fire Island (1 roll); Montauk '49, Interiors – Zackery, Beach Scenes (1 roll); Park Family (children) at Greene, New York (1 roll); Yorktown Heights, Eric and June Mose (1 roll); Untitled (5 rolls).
  - Unidentified Negatives, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Charlotte Park papers, 1930s-2010; Series 11; 3.6 Linear feet Boxes 15-18, OV 23
  This series is comprised of the professional and personal papers of Charlotte Park, Abstract Expressionist painter, art teacher, wife of James Brooks and executor of his estate.
  Biographical materials include notes about Park and other family members, copies of her birth certificate, and resumés.
  Correspondence consists of personal and business letters addressed to Charlotte and to the couple. In addition, there is correspondence concerning James Brooks' estate, posthumous exhibitions, and other business matters. Also found are copies of the correspondence of curator Meg Perlman and of Julie Lawrence Cochran, Director of the James Brooks and Charlotte Park Brooks Foundation.
  Writings by Park include 3 notebooks. Also included are a diary kept during a trip to Japan, and miscellaneous notes. Writings by others are a catalog essay on James Brooks, a poem by Stanley Kunitz, and one by Hilda Morley written for Park’s 1979 show at The Laundry.
  Among the subject files is documentation of Park's participation in the Art Lending Service of the Museum of Modern Art, her teaching activities, and interest in the women's movement. Other files concern The James Brooks and Charlotte Park Brooks Foundation, The Pollock-Krasner Foundation, Inc., and a James Brooks catalogue raisonné project. Exhibition files document Park exhibitions, posthumous Brooks exhibitions, and a show that included work by both.
  Personal business records include inventories, price lists, conservation records, sales, inventories, and gifts of artwork documenting Park's career, Brooks estate business and management of his artwork.
  Printed material consists of articles, exhibition announcements, catalogs, and miscellaneous items relating to Charlotte Park and James Brooks. Material concerning Brooks was published after his death.
  Artwork consists of two ink drawings: one by Abbott Pattison inscribed "St. Charlotte to me Abbott Pattison," and an unsigned portrait of an unidentified man.
  Photographic materials are photographs, negatives, slides, and color transparencies. Subjects are artwork by Park and views of a few Park exhibition installations. There are pictures of Charlotte Park alone and with friends, students, and her parents. Also found are views of the graves of various Hawkes-Park family members. A small photograph album consists of snapshots of Charlotte Park and Jim Brooks, unidentified friends, and cats.
  - Biographical Materials, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, circa 1930s-1999 (Box 15, Folder 15-23)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - Writings by Park, Diary of Trip to Japan, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Writings by Park, Notebooks, 1959-1963; 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Park, Notes, 1992; undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Writings by Others, Catalog Essay, "James Brooks: The Strong, Silent Type" by Sara K. Rich, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Writings by Others, Poems, undated; 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files (Box 16)
    - Art Lending Service, Museum of Modern Art, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - James Brooks: A Catalogue Raisonné, circa 1998-2008 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
    - James Brooks and Charlotte Park Brooks Foundation, circa 2002-2008 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - The Pollock-Krasner Foundation, Inc., 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Quotations about Art typed by Cile Downs, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Teaching, circa 1955-1967 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Type Samples, Hampton Press, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Women's Group, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Brooks Exhibitions (Box 16)
    - ACA Galleries, Munich, James Brooks: Works from the 50s and 60s (1999 March 4-May 29) (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Artemis-Greenberg Van Doren Gallery, James Brooks: Selected Paintings: 1960-1985 (2003 October 8-November 5), 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Greenberg Van Doren Gallery Exhibition (2005 Fall) (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Guild Hall, James Brooks in Retrospect (2001 October 6 -2002 January 6), 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 20-21)
    - Manny Silverman Gallery Exhibition (2005) (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - The Parrish Art Museum, The Stamp of Impulse: Abstract Expressionist Prints (2002 August 4-October 13) (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - The Sage Colleges, The New York School: Another View (2005 January 24-March 30), 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Tampa Museum of Art, Modern Art in Florida: 1948-1970 (2003 April 22-July 15) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Brooks and Park Exhibition, Spanierman Gallery, L.L.C., Artists and Nature on Eastern Long Island: 1940-the Present (2005 July 22-September 2) (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Park Exhibitions (Box 16)
    - Anita Shapolsky, Women of the 50's (2002 September 25-November 23) (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Elinor Poindexter Gallery, Joellen Hall, Cile Downs, Mary Lincoln Bonnel, Betty Klavun, Charlotte Park (1984 December 1-26), 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 28-29)
    - Ingberger Gallery, Ltd. Show (1979 December 1-19), 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Personal Business Records (Box 16)
    - Auction Records, Brooks, 1993-2005 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Bills, Paid, 1993-2005 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Conservation, Brooks, 1994-2008 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Conservation, Park, 2002-2005 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Conservation, Other Artists, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Gifts, Artwork by Brooks (Box 16)
      - The Brooklyn Museum, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Columbia Museum of Art, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - The Farnsworth Art Museum, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - Dan Flavin, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 39)
      - Norton Museum of Art, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      - The Portland Art Museum, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      - Southern Methodist University, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      - Telfair Museum of Art, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Gifts, Artwork by Park, 2001-2004; 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Insurance, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Inventories, Brooks, 1992; undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Inventories, Brooks Paintings at Crozier, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Inventories, Brooks Works on Paper, circa 1994-2005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Inventories, Park, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Lists of Paintings by Park, circa 1970s-2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Loans, Brooks and Park, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Loans, Park, 1970s-2004 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Mailing Lists, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Prices, Brooks, circa 1993-2004 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Prices, Park, circa 1965-1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Publication/Reproduction Permissions, Brooks, 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Receipts, Brooks, 1992-2003 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Receipts, Park, 1959; 1974-2001 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Royalties (VAGA), Brooks, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Sales, Brooks, 1992-2005 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Sales, Park, circa 1959-1985 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Storage, Park, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Storage and Shipping, Brooks, circa 1994-2008 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Walsh, John (Attorney, Estate of James Brooks), 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Washburn Gallery Agreement, Brooks, 1992-1998 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Printed Material, undated (Box 17)
    - Articles about/mentioning Charlotte Park, circa 1945-2002 (Box 17, Folder 23-25)
    - Articles about/mentioning James Brooks, 1992-2003 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Articles, Miscellaneous, circa 1949-2005 (Box 17, Folder 27-30)
    - Exhibition Announcements, Brooks, 1993-2003 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Exhibition Announcements, Other Artists, circa 1950-2001 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Exhibition Announcements, Park, circa 1953-2003 (Box 17, Folder 33-35)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Brooks, 1994-1996 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Brooks, 1997-2006 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Other Artists, 1961-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3-8)
      Other Finding Aids note
      Oversized material housed in OV 23.
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Park, circa 1953-1986 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Items mentioning Brooks, circa 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Items mentioning Park, 1974-1995 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Items, circa 1972-2004; Oversized material housed in OV 23. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Obituaries, circa 1950s-2002 (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
  - Artwork, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Photographic Materials (Box 18)
    - Artwork by Park, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Artwork by Park (Negatives), undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Artwork by Park (Slides), circa 1970s-1987 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Artwork by Others, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Exhibition Installations, Mathews Gallery, Houston, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Exhibition Installations, The Parrish Art Museum, Three East End Artists (2003) (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition Installations, Unidentified Venue, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Charlotte Park, circa 1940s-2004; Includes negatives and slides. (Box 18, Folder 24-25)
    - Charlotte Park at Muir Woods (1945), undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Charlotte Park in Studio [with curator Meg Perlman?], 1990s (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Charlotte Park with Others, 1962-2001; 1940s (Box 18, Folder 28-29)
    - Park Family, circa 1979-1982 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Photograph Album, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Hawkes-Park Family Graves, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Oversized Exhibition Catalogs, Other Artists, from box 18, Folder 6, 1974 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Miscellaneous Printed Items, General, from Box 18, Folder 13, undated (Box OV 23)